# **Furkan Karaca**

Ankara, Turkey



devfkn@gmail.com



5068626431



linkedin.com/in/fkrc

# **Summary**

I have been involved in software development for about 4 years. Initially, I started developing games with Unity and C#. After 1 year, my interests changed and I started developing Frontend. When I first started web development, I started to earn small income with the Wordpress pages I made as a freelance, and then I settled into my first full-time job using Opencart and Woocommerce. Here I developed myself and gained experience with SEO, SQL, JavaScript and React. I am as self taught person, got to this point by working and learning on my own without any help from anyone. From now on, my only desire is to climb the career ladder even faster with the experience I have gained.

### **Experience**



### vi∈v Web Developer

Viev Mobilya

Jul 2020 - Present (2 years 3 months +)

I set up 3 different web pages belonging to Viev Mobilya, which is one of the first companies to open e-commerce among furniture companies in Turkey. I did the SEO work of the web pages and design all the images (slider, banner, etc.) used on the pages. I run E-commerce businesses such as product tracking, stock control, adding new products, editing photos of products, at the same time manage the advertising accounts of the company. I prepare advertisement images and share advertisements in different languages for Turkey and Europe via Google Ads.



#### Intern

Nish Business Solutions

Aug 2019 - Oct 2019 (3 months)

I was an intern in a company that provides consultancy in the field of business management and business follow-up to one of the Turkey's largest telecommunication companies. Here I have been working on SQL on user data and i gained experience in SQL and Java.



### **Web Development Intern**

Noir Pro Studio

Jun 2019 - Aug 2019 (3 months)

I have designed web pages for companies from different sectors through wordpress within an advertising agency. I also carried out the SEO of these pages.

#### Education



### Ankara University

Bilgisayar Programlama Sep 2020 - Jun 2022

# **Licenses & Certifications**



# Kodluyoruz Akademi

Issued Jun 2021 - Expires Jul 2021

# **Skills**

JavaScript • React.js • Adobe Photoshop • HTML • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • WordPress • Opencart • Adobe Illustrator • SQL • C#